

# LOGAN SCANDLING RUNDQUIST

GRAPHIC AND
MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER

#### PROFILE

Hi, my name is Logan and I am a graphic designer with a versatile art background. I am garnering in-house graphic design experience in my current position, and in early 2020 I completed Design Bootcamp from School of Motion. My background in art allows me to use my creative eye to tackle any issue head on.

### ONLINE PORTFOLIO

WWW.LSRCREATIVE.COM

## CONTACT ME

(817) 905-5963 LoganTScandling@gmail.com



## EXPERIENCE

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

2020 TX Service Life Insurance | Oct 2020 - Present

Creating forms to assist agents, re-branding documents, creating custom graphics, print and digital items for our brands and funeral homes.

#### MARKETING COORDINATOR

2017 CWS Corporate Housing | June 2017 - Mar 2020

Devised and implemented marketing plans to generate leads for various markets. Purchasing, allocation and inventory of physical collateral. Graphic design work consisted of print and digital material, presentations, social media and brand management.

#### SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER & PHOTO ASSISTANT

2016 Mulberry4Baby Photography | Oct 2016 - Jan 2017

Managed social media accounts and developed social media strategy to increase brand engagement. Staged shoots, styled clients, organized photos, attended events and assisted with onsite shoots



## EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS, MAJOR IN STUDIO ART

Baylor University | 2011 - 2015



# ACHIEVEMENTS

**DESIGN BOOTCAMP: SCHOOL OF MOTION** 

Designing for Motion | June 2020

WEBSITE REDESIGN COLLAB- START TO FINISH

Led project for CWS Corporate Housing & Home Services | 2018

PRESIDENT'S VOLUNTEER SERVICE AWARD

Bronze: 100 hours | 2019 Bronze: 135 hours | 2018

**ACADEMIC HONOR LIST & DEAN'S SCHOLARSHIP** 

Dean's Gold Scholarship: Baylor University | 2014-15



# SKILLS

Digital Marketing

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Lightroom

Microsoft Office Suite

Social Media Management

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Canva